Pai
Hi Hi
assalamualaikum I really want to search
Hey 28 years old
[Music]
Kai okay now I want to share 20
singer safiles as Cintaku
by Shena function here sort out
events as permission
[Music]
used to go to Jeddah oteng
even now but we go in drinking
that know 50% salary cut circumcision land
to find income to be known
safrijal
year when Syahrini made one so it's not
as simple as wedding money too
[Music]
Okay so tomorrow this week but one
most important seed as Soraya
my love count to help people
Kites in Yi completion someone wants
Replacement earlier to realize
equality advertising suddenly Aditya who is
mysterious but definitely
adjusted
to Citra
in
our police people run away extreme sport so that
article 365 wife but definitely ricis dead
pain and title misfortune on
Google this fried tofu fried tofu location
Kind of one hour khaya or if I
see Aisha I die I can't I know
not so mysterious but so comfortable
definitely promise prologue Swag has called abi
nahkoda to become an ally to  cool guitar
full we provide that choice we
this Coral happened your crew this please
buy you or fortune I mentioned earlier
to move the risk of the
most important seeds and needs for
everyone wijdan berkah Okay hibatun
channel for example finished
died
again out can try to leave the
arrival for Blora continue
their lives for the left
future or day My life Geisha will be
guaranteed with her science satriyanti
Second Monday appears less necessary charity is
medicare medicaid apple Okay if you
sweater misfortune or illness
mousefeet visit it will be covered FB Takaful
[Music]
Ready
with that Koramil savings Bun
saved because everything
[Music]
Hi
bentosa satui about investment or
sewing in Takaful if a sick person
is thrown into a ravine is no longer allowed DJ
Caca Khalil scan accident or illness FB
Takaful will pay every year
because Paula knows more
what is useful to join Sorry Ashley,
we will help a little cat DVD
[Music]